It's time for another episode of Upcomi, this time with Rei Inoue of Juice-Juice and Kokoro Maeda of Beyonds and Amemori Kawa!
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll be showing you the process of recording, rehearsals, and other production processes of our artists.
I, Inoue, am a fan of Juice-Juice.
Juice-Juice celebrated the 10th anniversary of their major label debut on September 11!
I, Inoue, am very happy to hear that.
Thank you very much.
We had an event.
There were many members who were making toasts for the first time in a long time, which made me very happy.
It was a bit emotional and emo.
It was really a very stimulating 3 days.
Yes, I'm going to talk about the 25th anniversary concert.
It was really a gorgeous concert with many original members performing.
I was watching the performance from the backstage, and I was so moved that I had goosebumps all the time.
I was so moved that I couldn't stop getting goosebumps.
I was so moved that I couldn't stop the goosebumps from coming out of my mouth.
Even after the show was over, I was so immersed in the afterglow that I kept looking back at the video footage.
It was a really fun experience for me.
Beyonds sang a super happy song with Mr. Elijah.
He was so kind to me from the rehearsal.
Also, Airi Suzuki and Maimi Yajima of ℃-ute sang a song by ℃-ute with the current members.
I was also very happy to hear that Airi Suzuki and Maimi Yajima from ℃-ute were singing songs by ℃-ute with the current members, and they said that they would sing together with me someday. I am very happy to hear that they are encouraging the current members to sing together, and I will do my best more and more since we became a principle member.
Let's start with this time's up-kami, here.
Or the Tsubaki Factory! From the mill, but it's okay! Please take a look at how we filmed the music video for I say I'm lost.
You're lost in the middle of the place you can see.
I'm off! I'm looking forward to it! How long can it last, just a little too late for us to meet?
But this is true love
The strength to hold on
I can't help but be convinced
The shooting of the music video for "But It's OK" has begun!
We started early this morning
I came to the forest to shoot some image scenes.
I don't do a lot of hand gestures or anything like that.
We didn't do a lot of hand gestures or anything like that.
I didn't do a lot of hand gestures or anything like that, but mainly facial expressions.
I thought it was very difficult to convey the lyrics with facial expressions alone.
I thought it was very difficult to convey the lyrics with just facial expressions, but each of them had their own expression and personality, and I was looking forward to seeing their sensitivities.
I hope you're looking forward to it too.
I don't know. It's a lie, forever.
I want the worst kind of love.
I want to practice.
I want to practice... get down high, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I want to go lower, a little wider, and fail to notice, especially when I'm at my limit.
I met you just a little too late, but I'm convinced it's true love, and I'm strong enough to hold on to it.
Gentle kisses, Rusty Rolling.
Where are you going back to? I know, but miss swing
I don't care if it's someone else's you, just fool me perfectly.
I love you. I love you so much I wonder who you are.
To be sad. To pull it out.
I want to see the end of the world, there are no questions in this world
So this is a lie, forever a meme
Can I ask everyone to gather round?
Please, please, please, please.
Please give me a camera.
I believe in you so much.
Okay, everybody, we're done.
Thank you for your hard work.
You were on location this time, right?
Yes, it was.
The scene, or rather, the PC.
It was a shooting in the forest,
It was my first time shooting in the forest,
I think it was the first time for everyone.
It's not often you get to go out in the forest like that.
It was a very valuable experience,
It was a very valuable experience, and I was able to feel the atmosphere while filming the performance,
I think it was a great experience.
I took a lot of pictures of everyone's objects,
It was great to be able to photograph them.
I was covered in wine spoons,
And the dance scene.
It felt like a live performance, like there was an audience in front of us.
I felt like there was an audience in front of me, so I wanted to perform the song in front of them. It was a lot of fun. I hope you all enjoy it.
It was really fantastic and everyone looked beautiful in the natural setting.
I thought the different angles and ways of showing them were very individualistic, and the use of a lot of smoke in the shooting made me feel like I was watching the whole thing from a different angle.
The way they used a lot of smoke in the shooting looked like a lot of fun.
It's a sad song, but when it came to the making of the song, I could see everyone having fun, and it made me feel like I was sharing my happiness with them.
That's all for the making of the music video shooting at Tsubaki Factory.
Tsubaki Factory or Not, September 27, Onseion
Thanks for watching after a long time!
Next up is JuiceJuice PRIDE BRITE Vocal RecordingJuiceJuice's latest single, PRIDE BRITE Emada 孎崎's vocal recording.
How are you feeling? I was a little nervous.
But the vibe is really good.
I was hoping that he would be more like Emasaki and go with the rhythm,
and if you can do an accent, that's all I ask.
I hope you can get the accent.
Let's go to 4 songs.
Yes.
Well, well..,
It suits her, doesn't it?
I'm not a woman who can call it a clean slate.
I'm not the kind of girl who can compare and congratulate herself for being chosen.
You're very conscious of her.
I'm very aware of it now.
In terms of where I'm going to hang up next time...
I'm conscious of cutting it now.
But when I think about the timing of the cut...
I'm thinking about the timing of the cut.
I hope I can be aware of where to make the cut.
I hope to be able to be aware of the timing of the cut.
I'm a little fuzzy on that right now, so I'll just say it in my head.
If I say it in my head
It's the same for that girl.
When you continue the same melody like "da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da"...
I'm just saying, "I'm that girl now," and I'm cutting in the same way.
It's like, "I'm that girl now," because you're cutting in a way that says
The timing of the cut is also the same.
Yes, yes, yes.
So it was right.
I'm not the kind of woman who can say, "Congratulations," because this part is pretty old.
When I say I'm not a woman who can say "me-too"...
I'm not a woman.
Let's give it one more push at the "not a woman" part.
I'm not a woman, I'm not a woman, I'm not a woman.
I'm not a woman who can say "thank you
I'm not a woman who can say "thank you.
Okay, just like that.
She's pissed.
Okay, good luck. Let's do it like that.
Let's go to B melody.
I'm so happy that I've been chosen over you... and I can say that I'm not the only one or the number one...
There are different reasons to fall in love
Only one or number one
I'm in love with both
Either one is cool.
And the entrance
Only one is still a bit loose.
I still feel it's a little loose, so I'm going to sing it firmly.
I hope I can sing the first line well.
Yes. The Orihane number is "Each of us has his own reasons for falling in love.
Ori ena number, I'm in love with both of them.
OK, that's good!
OK, then, the chorus.
You can't get enough of it?
Yes!
Are you sure?
Keep it up! Hold on to the pride, the pride you couldn't take away
Only one and number one
No, no, no, look forward
Pride that I couldn't give even to you
So cool!
Wow, something totally different from before, something totally different about Pride
Bakkong!
That's soooo good!
One thing to keep in mind
I think you can sing it really cool now.
I think it would be better if the orchestra can cut it a little more firmly
If you can cut the orchestra
I'll be able to get into it better.
I will be able to sing more and more coolly.
And just in terms of the words
The pride at the end
The pride that you couldn't give me or you couldn't give me
Let's be a little more conscious of the "Do
Now that it's become a ply...
So, yes, yes, like this.
Just be a little more conscious of the "Do".
Yes, yes...
Okay, let's try one more time Only one and number one I wanted to love you both
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't. No planned kisses.
Even you couldn't take it away from me, PRIDE, PRIDE
Only one and number one, no, no, no, look forward
Even for you I couldn't give you my pride
It's so good!
It's so cool all of a sudden.
Is it like that?
Like this?
Pride, pride, pride...
Bride Bride here.
It still stings a little bit.
Sometimes it disappears a little bit.
I'm a little girl, I wanted to love you, I couldn't love you
I couldn't love you. I couldn't love you. I couldn't love you.
You couldn't even take me away from you.
Pride, pride, pride.
Only one.
No, no, no, face forward
The pride that even you couldn't take away
I'm totally okay with it.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This song...
I think the first thing that comes to mind is that it's pretty cool.
But when you read the lyrics, it's not about a cool girl.
It's a song about a girl who can't let go of her pride, and from my point of view, I think she's kind of cute.
So there's a gap between the two.
I thought it was difficult to express that in the song.
It was really in the song...
The Voice of Heaven
I heard Mr. Uemura's voice from the heavens.
The recording session was very lively and enjoyable.
I don't mean to say that this was the usual way...
But it wasn't.
I heard from Eva that Mr. Kamimura was the one who recorded the song.
I just learned from Eva that it was like this,
It was interesting.
I felt like a free goddess, and I thought it was very typical of Akari Uemura,
I think it's great that you praised me during the recording session, because it made me realize how good I was.
I think Hisanori Ebata's voice is unique, and all the members of JuiceJuice have great voices, so I thought her voice was wonderful.
I love this song, too, and she's been telling me about it ever since the first performance.
I thought "Wow, I love this song!
I love it so much that I watch the music video and the live video on repeat everyday.
I was so happy to see the recording video this time.
Thank you so much!
I'm looking forward to listening to it a lot more!
That's all for Juice-Juice Pride of Light's vocal recording of Kisaki Karada.
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual.
JuiceJuice's Innovate Beyons Amamori Kami's Upcoming Paper by Kokoro Maeda
Next up is here... Ochanoma, a little emotional instability, summer, vocal recording.
From the latest single by Ochanoma, "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer." Here's a look at the vocal recording by Maki Saito.
I'm going to start with the A melody.
When I told her my ideal type, she said, "You're strange.
Oh oh
The second part is a little more...
I don't know...
You look like you're having fun.
She seems happy.
Yes, the way the guy who's 6 centimeters off the ground is saying it...
Yeah, it sounds like fun... the way a guy who's 6 centimeters off the school says it.
It's different from my ideal type... like now, I'm in trouble.
How did you handle it?
Like, "I'm in trouble, I'm not like other people.
Can I do more of that?
Yes.
I like it when the ideal is stronger.
I'll go one more time... you think you're dressed up, but you're unique.
When I say ideal type, she says I'm strange.
Oh, oh, oh...
Can I just do the last one?
I don't think he's changed at all.
Really? He's like...
He's a little angry.
He's a little troubled. Yes.
Yes. I'll do just that.
Yes, I'll do that.
Oh, I'll do this.
Yes.
Then, B melody.
This one, um...
Yes. Yes. And then the melody, the collage, the collage of emotion, the reverb of love, the wave of passion, and then the B melody.
Yes, this one is higher.
Wave of passion Heated curve
And the curve, I want the brightness to go eat.
Yes
Collage of Emotions Reverb of Affection
Wave of passion Heating or boo
Heating or smoothness
Boo emotion good.
I knew it. I want more of an anterior bullet head attack.
Yes, okay.
Carr, uh, Joe.
Yes, yes, I got it.
Yes, perfect. Rust!
Rust! Rust! Oh no!
Emotional instability is going down a bit.
It's going down with "I". Unstable is...
Uncertain? Yes, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite, indefinite is indefinite.
Yes, unstable is down, indefinite is keep, season is down, I'll give it a try, but it's a little bit too much.
I'll try a little more...
I made a mistake.
What is it?
I've already put the melody in the bass line.
I'll sing the melody, and then you can sing the rest of the song.
Yes, sir.
Let's do it on the stage, then.
I want it to be rhythmic, and I want the tension to be really high.
Make it sound like a chorus.
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder if it's the summer, or if I'm dreaming, or if I'm just a little unstable.
I wonder whose fault it is, I wonder if it's yours, I wonder if it's yours, I'm not sure who it is
Bunkei, ahkei, ayapan, I'm going to lose my orchestra a little bit up there, but I don't want you to become weak in that upper-tonal instability. Sansan, burn. I may or may not take the gaya. He said it was good to have the image of taking it.
Yes, I understand.
I want it to have melody, but I want it to have momentum. There. The sun is shining, fireworks are the band, it's the flashy season, a woman's heart and
Summer sky, whimsy, whimsy, seven changes
Chotto chotto, unstable summer
It's nice. I'll only shoot the flashy season with this.
Pitch.
It's the flashy season. Pitch.
It's a flashy seasonal lyric.
OK, let's just end it at this moment.
OK, I get it!
Yes, the recording session looked like a lot of fun!
You looked like you were having so much fun!
Your facial expressions were so lively, and you were singing with a smile on your face the whole time,
I also got the impression that she had a gap between her own voice and her singing voice,
Really!
Her singing voice was so cute, she sounded like a cartoon character.
It was easy to imagine what kind of songs she usually listens to, but when I actually talked to her, she told me that she likes this kind of music, so I wanted to talk to her about it. I could feel that everyone at Ochanoma is really good at self-production and studying how to showcase themselves, so I'm really looking forward to the future.
This was the vocal recording of Makoto Saito in the slightly emotionally unstable summer of Ochanoma.
I'm sure something good will happen!
This was the time to say goodbye to the depths of the experience that Innomerate and Kokoro Maeda have brought to you. I learned a lot from watching so many videos this time, and I was also impressed by how everyone was able to put the detailed instructions into practice.
I was impressed by how well everyone put the detailed instructions into practice.
Personally, I want to sing "Pride Bright" someday.
I want to sing it someday.
I want to sing it!
I want to watch this video a lot and learn from it.
I'd like to watch and learn a lot from this video.
I'd like to watch it when they perform it.
I watched the making of Tsubaki Factory's music video.
I'd like to see the making of Tsubaki Factory's music videos and see how they do it.
I think it's easy to see the characteristics of the group behind the scenes.
It was a great experience for me to be able to see it.
It was a lot of fun. I think it was a good thing to see.
I also thought the interactions between the members were very cute.
Maybe I feel the same way as you are looking at this.
I feel the same way. It was a lot of fun.
In Abu-Kami, we will be going behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see.
This time, UpCami is joined by Reine Inoue of Juice-Juice!
Beyonds It was Maeda Shin of Amamori Kami.
Good bye.
Next time on upcami,
Tsubaki Factory: If you're just delusional, you're free!
and
recording session of "Ai no Kedamono" by Anjelum!
Enjoy, and see, we're already hooked.
Burning encounters are on the verge of extinction